Iinari Expedition
Ikuta Shinji
Kitami Satone
I look forward to working with you.
We are the Iinari Expedition.
What are you two going to do today?
Today's exploration is
Let's explore Second Street!
Second Street is located on the basement floor of eBean's.
How about you two? Have you ever been to Second Street?
No, I have not. No, I haven't.
No? !
It's nice to meet you.
It's your first time. First Street, isn't it?
You're so noisy. You're definitely making fun of me.
We had the two of us explore the area together, and Second Street is also in the business of buying things.
Today, we asked the two of you to bring in some of your personal belongings to be evaluated, so we thought we'd have you explore the store while we did that too.
So, we'd like to have them explore the shop while we do that. Let's move on to the store.
Well, we've arrived at Second Street.
Yes! Here we are!
It's today, isn't it?
I'm Mr. Kudo, the manager of Second Street. Nice to meet you.
Please give me a warm welcome.
Mr. Kudo, this is the first time for two of us to visit Second Street.
May I first ask you to explain what kind of store Second Street is?
Second Street has more than 750 stores nationwide.
Second Street has more than 750 stores nationwide, selling all kinds of items from clothes to furniture, home appliances, hobby goods, and sporting goods, and offering a wide variety of goods.
Second Street is a view store that has more than 750 stores nationwide and offers a wide variety of items ranging from clothing to furniture, home electronics, hobby goods, and sporting goods.
Our Second Street Sendai Ekimae E-Beans store is located on the first basement floor of E-Beans.
E-Beans, located on the first basement floor.
We are open from 10:00 to 20:00.
I see.
Do you understand? Pearl.
Yes, I understand.
In other words, what kind of store is it?
From 10:00 to 20:00.
There!
That's the last minute, isn't it?
Well, I mean, it's a nice store.
Open for business.
So I'm really looking forward to it.
Opening hours are important, right?
Yes, it's important.
I'd like to take a look around the store first.
If you have any questions or concerns, please let me know.
If you have any questions or concerns, just ask manager Kudo.
If you have any questions or concerns, please ask manager Kudo.
First, let's take a look around the store.
Okay, let's go around.
Let's go around.
Let's go!
It's huge.
It's really big.
It's my first time, so I'm excited.
Wow, look at this. Look at the fishing rods.
Where's the fishing?
Have you ever been fishing?
No, I haven't.
Not this one.
You put some kind of clay on it, and then you put it in the pond...
Mr. Isai!
It's something, isn't it?
I understand. I'll put something like clay on it.
A fishing pond?
Yes.
This kind of thing is made of wakasagi or something...
Real ones.
I'd like to try it.
Look! It's got isai in it!
Mr. Shishichi!
Shishamachi!
I'll tell my boyfriend.
Sure thing!
How much is it?
4,900 yen.
It's signed, right?
That's amazing.
They have everything.
Around here.
Toys.
It's Ultraman!
What is it?
I returned 10 of them.
That's fine.
I've got Sylvanians and stuff.
Sylvanians!
What's so different about them?
Ten Sylvanian Families.
What's this?
Do you like it?
Is it a big house?
Is it this one?
Rine used to have one of these.
I gave it to my cousin.
You didn't sell it to your cousin?
That's right.
Is this it?
Interesting.
But I regret giving it to him.
That's true.
Now that I've seen it, it's too much.Now that it's more than ever.
Now that I am more aware of the value of these things...
I think it's possible.
If you had them in your room now.
It would make a great interior decoration.
I have one in my rough house.
Which one?
A fun zoo.
This lion cub was so popular at the time that there was a lot of competition for it, so I decided to buy one for my house.
I remember buying it. They made all kinds of things. That's my creativity. That's my creativity.
I have a fun one. I want one.
It can communicate wirelessly. With this, you could put one in the backstage area at a live concert, where one person is in the backstage and says, "It's about to start soon.
That would be great!
You just have to go and time it right.
Why do you make them go alone at first?
There are appliances and so on.
It's amazing.
It's really delicious!
I wonder if it's got those balls in it... I don't know, but...
Electric guns are cool too!
A cup is cool just because you have it.
So it's not a real gun, it's a real gun, it says so!
I don't want to fight in a cover-all-the-people game with this!
How are we going to fight?
If I really hit it, it'll hurt.
What's this thing?
But I want one... the Sinanju I have...
I'm like a fish out of water.
I've got a Sinanju... like a fish out of water.
I'm so excited...
I'm talking without continuing... it's like a dream come true.
You can make them and hang them up!
It's on display.
Look at her! She's like a woman in winter!
You're busy.
You don't have to flutter your hair so much.
Doesn't it look so new?
It's so beautiful.
The manager said you have used merchandise, but you also have new merchandise.
This one's brand new.
There's so much here.
They're arranged a little differently from the others.
Amazing.
It's like a dream.
Isn't this stuff so good?
Where are you going?
I'm going to a concert now.
Oh, wow.
Your wife's concert.
What do you think?
It looks good on you.
It's cute.
What do you want me to say?
What's the right word?
I'd say it's mature.
It's cool.
Cute and cool! Thank you!
It's so mature!
Nice!
Is this okay?
Thank you very much!
Okay, so we've been over here in the brands section, and we've got a little mini-game going on.
We're going to play a little mini-game here.
I'd like to play a little mini-game.
I'd like to play a game.
I've got all these Viton bags here that you saw earlier.
I'll ask each of you to choose one of the bags on the shelf.
I'll ask you both to choose one of the bags on the shelf, and I'll ask you to choose which one is more expensive.
Let's have a quick look and see which one you can choose.
Okay.
There's also the size.
That's right.
I think it's big.
It's not the same if gold is expensive or not.
I see.
That's right.
It's the same.
Which one?
This one.
Bottom row.
Second from the right.
This one.
This is the most expensive one for both of us.
Because it's the biggest one.
Oh, and it's got a bathtub.
Well, we're kind of in the same boat.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to win.
The loser is forced to choose a different one.
I'll take "goo" rock-paper-scissors.
Oh!
Shinju got it.
Don't pick the next biggest one.
Why don't we pick the biggest one?
I thought it was bigger than I expected.
It's big.
And I'm using this.
It's like we're the first two people to buy a pair of Vitons.
It's big.
Is it big or small by your standards?
What about the weight?
Weight depends on what's inside.The weight depends on what's inside, doesn't it?
Let's take a look at the price from Ms. Kitami's side.
The price of this bag is
87,900 yen.
Wow!
This is not a showcase.
It's right here, like this.
And it's right by the front door.
The front door?
My friend.
Right there.
There's security all over the neighborhood.
I'm sure it's safe.
Eighty-seven thousand nine hundred yen.
Then please announce the price of
Shinju-san, please announce the price of this bag.
Eh?
64,900 yen.
So that means
First place winner, Mekikio, is Kitamiri.
It's a real draw.
No, I knew that.
It was a dare.
I thought it would be better to make it interesting.
I thought it would be more interesting.
He lost a rock-paper-scissors-scissors game on a dare.
The odds are stacked against us.
They've brought their personal belongings today.
I thought I'd ask you to evaluate them.
May I see what you brought?
I'll start with this.
It was made on October 22nd, 2013.
Moss pearls.
My handmade moss paper.
You made it yourself? I even painted it.
Yes, we make moss paper in school.
I'm sure you do.
It's been hanging in my house ever since.
That's what I brought with me today.
I see.
And now, here we go...
What's this?
This is my treasure.
I found it in the schoolyard when I was a kid.
I collected the cleanest sand I could find
I collected and carefully selected.
Nice.
It's sparkling.
I'd collect it, but when I was a kid, I used to say it was a diamond.
In my mind, it's a diamond.
I'm sure this is very expensive.
You used to collect them.
It's amazing that you still have it.
It really is.
It's on display with this.
So what?
And finally...
Ta-da!
Here it is!
Dragon Balls!
Ta-da!
It's amazing!
I want one!
It's really great.
No, no, no.
I really want it.
This is actually my blog.
It used to be on my old blog.
I did.
back in the day, when I was just starting out in the Northeast.
I was doing gigs in various places.
I got one from each of those places and
And here we are now.
Oh, really?
It exists.
I worked so hard to collect these Dragon Balls.
I've worked so hard to collect them.
But today, I'd like to give you a valuation.
Wow, that's great.
May I introduce you to Mr. Kitami?
Let's start with...
Ta-da!
So cute!
Is this...
As a baby.
This is my baby!
Probably just born in a hospital.
He's so cute.
Is he cute?
Oh, my hair.
But it's more like a baby than this face.
Most babies are like that.
I don't think so.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, it is.
She certainly has a lot of hair.
Yes, I'm sure.
Yes, I was born with a lot of hair.
You certainly have a lot of hairhair full of hair
Very lush!
Indeed, indeed, indeed.
It's really amazing.
You look like you were just born.
Oh, really?
That's amazing.
You just said you just noticed it.
It must be newborn.
He's got a lot of hair.
You know, I could probably sign this or something.
I'd get a lot of money for it.
That's what you brought me?
Yes, I did.
Oh, my God.
And the next one.
This one.
He's cute.
What is it? What is this doll?
I don't know what it is, but...
You don't bring me things I don't understand.
She's been in my room since I can't remember.
Before the picture.
I think so.
I asked your father about it.
He gave them to me.
All of these...
It's all handmade from scratch.
That's right.
He said they've been here since before I was born.
It was in the house.
When I was a little girl.
I had them in my doll room.
I had like 15 of them.
I had them all lined up in a row.
But this one...
It was so different from the others.
She's so scary.
But this one...
If you let her out of the room
I'm afraid she'll come back to the room at night
I'm afraid she'll come back to my room at night
I was really scared.
That's why I've been trying so hard to raise her.
It's a scary doll.
Scary story
But nothing ever happened to me
That's why I'm 20 years old now
I've probably had it for more than 20 years
I heard it was in the Kitami family
I heard it was all homemade.
So you brought it.
Rust.
Rust?
Ta-da!
What's this?
This is from
I graduated from Sendai Ikuei
I graduated from Sendai Ikuei.
What are you doing with that?
I've never opened it.
Actually, it's still taped up.
It's a graduation present.
Only those who graduated from Ikuei can get it.
Only graduates of Ikuei can get them.
It's marked.
In addition to this, I also got a fork.
I also got a fork.
You should save it.
This is...
I brought it just in case.
I'm from a winning school.
I want it.
If you want it, you might want it.
I see.
Okay, I'll give you these three things each.
I've brought something for each of you.
I'd like you to take a look at them.
I'd like you to take a look at them and see which one
Which one has the higher appraisal value?
The clerk will announce which one has the higher appraisal value.
I'd like you to announce the result right away.
I'd like you to announce the result.
Thank you very much.
Did it take you long?
Yes, it did.
I'll look into it.
I'll get right on it.
He said you made an announcement.
Please do.
The highest purchase price was...
Shinjuku
Yay!
This set of three is...
That's right.
I've decided... this one.
I've got Dragon Balls.
I've got seven Dragon Balls.
I can make my dreams come true.I can make my dreams come true.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're going to be in it?
You have a dream.
You can't beat the Dragon Balls.
By the way, other than the Drogonballs, where are the ones the two of you brought?
Yes, they are. They're dolls, and they're cute, but we can't buy them due to their condition.
Also, we are sorry that we cannot accept this photo and the graduation commemorative items.
That's a shocking fact, isn't it?
Also, we cannot accept these two items.
In short, we can only handle Drogonballs.
You mean you bought them at the price you could handle them?
Yes, that's right. But they are worth something.
What are you bringing?
I'm embarrassed.
Well, well, well, well, of course.
Now, let's say that Ms. Pearl is the winner in the current showdown.
I'm sorry to say that Kitami-san has lost.
Punishment game, it's not that big of a deal.
I'm going to ask you to accept it.
Kitami, can I ask you to close your eyes?
What, what, what?
What? Why are you smiling?
Well, Shun-san, can you turn them this way for a moment?
Ready?
Kitami's punishment game is now open to the public.
Why are you smiling?
It's cute.
Cute?
Kitami, can I ask you to open your eyes?
What is this?
Is it a baseball glove?
That's because I'm still Icue.
It's a picture of you as a child.
Wait a minute.
What? What?
We're playing a penalty game now, aren't we?
Don't edit anything.
It's a penalty game, right?
Punishment game, please.
We have our own way.
Uhhh...
What the hell?
May I see it?
Wait a minute.
I'm really going to make you do this.
Ehhhh...
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's get a few shots of each other.
We took a few pictures of each other.
Since we're here...
I'm in seventh grade or something.
That's a high, high straight. I was made to do this.
What's the policy on this pose?
You know what I'm talking about.
Cute bangs, too. Yes, I have bangs like this.
When did Shizu-san's bangs come off?
I like how she's brushing her teeth, it's like a commercial.
Oh no! There's a recent one too.
Cute! Here's the latest one.
Cute! Her hair is the same as now.
Oh no! Not cute!
Nice piece... with a finger in her face.
It's so old-fashioned... the quality of the image... it was taken with a lot of cameras.
It's cute.
That's the kind of work they're pushing her to do.
This is recent.
This is totally recent.
So you're still in the age of "no makeup"?
That's what I'm talking about.
So we're here at Second Street today.
Manager Kudo has an announcement to make.
Friday, November 25th at 10:00 a.m.
Monday, November 28th, 9:59 a.m.
We will have a web-only Black Friday Sale from 10:00 a.m. on Friday, November 25th to 9:59 p.m. on Monday, November 28th.
You can take advantage of a 10% discount on all qualifying Fall/Winter Alias purchases made through our online store!
Yes, please take advantage of it!
This time we are at Second Street!
What a lot of things!
It was so exciting and fun to watch the video!
They even filmed us!
I hope you all will come and visit us!
See you soon! Bye bye!
Thank you very much!